mycriminaljusticecareers2.com 2011-10-06

# Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy below describes the standards we adhere to in handling your personal information.

**Information Collection and Use**  
This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have signed up ("Consumers") on this website ("Web Site"), and other Renevati Inc. owned web sites that point to this site that may or may not be listed in this Privacy Policy. Please note that this pledge applies only to sites maintained by Renevati Inc. and not to web sites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. We may share the personal information that you supply to us with third party businesses in order to complete the request for additional information outlined by the Web Site. Requests for information will be fulfilled via direct mail, email and telemarketing. The third party businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing. You can browse the Mycriminaljusticecareers2 web site at anytime without revealing any personal information about yourself. There are, however, several areas on our web site where we collect personal information from you on a voluntary basis. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or phone number that is not otherwise publicly available. This information helps us serve you better by enabling us:

(1) to process and fulfill your requests for products and services  
(2) to solicit your opinions and other feedback  
(3) to conduct research  
(4) to customize the content you see  
(5) to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients

We may collect personal information at the following times:  
(1) when you register to receive communications from this website and other Renevati Inc. owned web sites  
(2) when you seek information or apply for products and services offered through this website and other Renevati Inc. owned web sites  
(3) when you enter promotions or sweepstakes offered by this website and other Renevati Inc. owned web sites  
(4) when you provide personal information to us through feedback, survery, or other forms hosted on this site and other Renevati Inc. owned websites  
(5) when you apply for a job with this website and other Renevati Inc. owned web sites  
In addition, we may receive information about you from other sources, such as service providers, for tracking purposes. We may add the information we receive about you to your existing account. Like other web sites, we also automatically receive and record certain types of information every time you visit us. We use "cookies" and the other information to enhance your experience and present you with personalized offers. Likewise, we sometimes use third-party advertising companies to serve and track advertisements appearing on our web site These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

**Legal Protection**  
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, and will establish or exercise our legal rights and defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Renevati's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

**Use and Sharing of PII**  
Renevati Inc. may share Consumer PII in aggregate, non-personal form, with select companies that wish to reach a particular Consumer target audience (e.g., registered female Consumers between the ages of 25-35, who have an average household income of over $50,000.00). This information will allow these entities to provide relevant offers to specific Consumers.  
Finally, Renevati Inc. may disclose Consumer PII in order to: (1) comply with applicable laws; (2) respond to governmental inquiries; (3) comply with valid legal process; and (4) protect the rights or property of Renevati Inc., the Network Sites or other Consumers of this Site.

**Business Transfer**  
As with any other business, it is possible that Renevati Inc. in the future could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by Renevati Inc., including customer account information. The successor company would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy unless you consent otherwise.

**Minors**  
You must be at least 18 years old to use this web site. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you can use the services offered on our web site only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. Please see our Terms of service for more information.

**Cookies and IP Addresses**  
To serve you more efficiently and effectively, we use "cookies" technology. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive that contains information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, a cookie simply terminates. Cookies enable a web site to "personalize" itself for each user and reduce the time it takes for pages to load on your computer. In order to optimize your experience, cookies also help with the collection of customer tracking data. We may also capture customer tracking data on some of our partner's web sites, realted to activity involved with the completion of offers listed on our web site. This information is used to monitor the performance of our partners. We also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

**Clear Gifs**  
We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movement of Web users. Clear gifs are not tied to users' personal information. We also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails the recipients have opened. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section within any email you receive from us or unsubscribe from our homepage by clicking here.

**Opting-Out**  
You may register to receive communications from us directly on our web site or through a third party. After registering, we will periodically send you newsletters and other e-mails featuring special offers, promotions, and other memberss-only benefits. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by clicking on the unsubscribe link contained within our emails. Our email database is updated continually. However, you may continue to receive email communications from us up to ten business days from the time we receive your unsubscribe request. Please note that Renevati Inc. can only control its own mailing list and policies. Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and you may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their email communications.

**Third Party Links**  
This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to Renevati Inc. However, when you visit web sites to which Mycriminaljusticecareers2 provides a link, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policy. If you choose to obtain certain services through a third party site, the data collected by the third party is governed by that third party's privacy policy. A third party site will also have its own policy regarding the use of cookies and clear gifs. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

If Renevati Inc. receives personal information from a third party that is not in conjunction with a service offered on our site, the use and disclosure of such information is governed by the agreement (if any) between Renevati Inc. and such third party.

**Updating Your Information**  
If you want to access or update the personal information you submitted to Mycriminaljusticecareers2 please e-mail us at service@mycriminaljusticecareers2.com or write us at the following address.

5255 North Edgewood Dr.  
Suite 225  
Provo, Utah 84604

**Questions and Suggestions** If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by sending an email to service@mycriminaljusticecareers2.com.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Renevati Inc. may update or modify this Privacy Policy. If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy or in how Renevati Inc. will use your personal information, we will post such changes here. You will be notified if any of the material changes affect the use of your personal information and asked to opt-in to the new use of your personal information. If you do not agree with the changes to how your information will be used, please do not continue to use this web site.

By using this site, you signify your assent to Renevati Inc. Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the Mycriminaljusticecareers2 site. When you request quotes or request to be contacted through Mycriminaljusticecareers2 or our other sites that we operate, you are authorizing us to share information with our business partners who will contact you by phone, email, or mail. If you do not want further communication from them, please notify the partner directly. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our web site to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our Privacy Policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Policy.

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
The following applies only to California residents.  
Renevati Inc., may, from time to time, share your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As a California resident, you have a legal right to request and receive in writing or by email the names and addresses of all such third parties who received your personally identifiable information during the previous calendar year and a list of the types of personally identifiable information disclosed to such third parties. To request such information, send an email to service@mycriminaljusticecareers2.com.

We will not honor such request more than once per calendar year.  
For more information on how your personally identifiable information is collected and used, please contact us by sending an email to service@mycriminaljusticecareers2.com.

PLEASE PRINT AND RETAIN A COPY OF THIS AGREEMENT FOR YOUR RECORDS.

LAST UPDATED 01-14-08
